Good morning, tiger.
老虎，早安
I'm making you a big breakfast, so you can keep up your strength for tonight.
我在幫你準備豐盛的早餐 這樣你才有辦法在今晚繼續奮戰
You're gonna get me good and pregnant.
你可要認真做，讓我懷孕
I've got nowhere to go this morning. I'm unemployed.
我今天早上竟然沒事 我失業了
I don't know what I'm gonna do with my life.
我不知道人生該怎麼辦才好
Well, I just lost my erection.
嗯，我沒有性趣了
No, I mean, what am I supposed to do with myself?
不，我是認真的 我的人生該怎麼辦呢？
You're supposed to find your passion in life.
你應該要找尋生命中的熱情
You can be whatever you want to be now. It's exciting.
你現在可以做任何你想要做的事 這是很刺激的
Yeah, but it's all so overwhelming. I don't know where to start.
是啊，但是這一切都太突然了 我不知道要如何開始
Wait a second. I can help you with this.
等一下，我可以幫你
You just need to be organized. We can make a list of your qualifications..
你只要整理好就行了 我們可以列出你的資歷
and categorize jobs by industry. There could be folders and files..
然後將工作機會以產業別做分類 可以用檔案夾跟檔案…
Hey, this is where your hyper-organized pain-in-the-ass stuff pays off.
嘿，這就是你超愛整理的偏執個性 派上用場的時候了
I know!
我知道！
My erection is back!
我又有性趣了！
The One Where Rachel Goes Back To Work
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Thank you.
謝謝
Joey, could I have a sip of your coffee and a bite of your muffin?
喬伊，我可以喝一口你的咖啡 跟吃一口你的鬆餅嗎？
- Okay. - Thank you.
-好的 -謝謝你
Thank you.
謝謝你
Phoebe, have you ever been bitten by a hungry Italian?
菲比，你有沒有被飢餓的 意大利人咬過呢？
I'm sorry. It's just, I'm a little short on cash.
我很抱歉，只是我最近手頭有點緊
If you want, I could loan you some money.
如果你有需要，我可以借你一些錢
Oh, no. I learned never to borrow money from friends.
喔，不，我已經得過教訓 千萬別跟朋友借錢
That's why Richard Dreyfuss and I don't speak anymore.
那就是為什麼 Richard Dreyfuss不再跟我說話的原因
Why don't you just spunge off your boyfriend?
你何不跟你男朋友拿呢？
Yeah, right, the unemployed piano player who gave his trust fund to charity?
是喔，那個把信託基金全捐給 慈善機構的失業鋼琴師嗎？
I'm splitting the muffin with him.
我要回去跟他分那個鬆餅的
Hey, how about this? Wanna be an extra on my show?
嘿，要不要這樣？ 來當我們電視劇的臨時演員？
You could do that?
可以嗎？
The pay's pretty good, and you could do it for as long as you need.
錢還不錯，而且只要 你有需要就可以做
- Oh, my God. I'm gonna be on TV! - Okay, now..
-喔，我的天，我要上電視了！ -好了，現在…
I gotta tell you, being on TV isn't as glamorous and exciting as you think.
我必須告訴你，上電視並不像你想像的 那樣光鮮亮麗跟好玩
- Really? - No, it is awesome.
-真的嗎？ -沒錯
比你想的更棒
Hey, guys.
嗨，你們好
Why are you all dressed up?
為什麼你們穿的這麼正式？
We're bringing Emma to Ralph Lauren today to introduce her to everyone.
我們要帶艾□去洛夫羅倫跟大家見面
- Doesn't she look cute? - She sure does.
-她看起來真是可愛吧？ -當然很可愛
Why does she have a pink bow taped to her head?
為什麼要貼那個粉紅色的 蝴蝶結在她頭上呢？
Because if one more person says, "What a cute little boy"..
因為如果再有人說 「真是個可愛的小男生…」
I'm gonna whip them with a car antenna.
我會用車子的天線鞭打他們
I think she's gonna be the hit of the office.
我想她會是辦公室裡面最時髦的
Yeah, she's gonna be hotter than peasant blouses and A-line skirts.
是啊，她一定會比那些 農家女上衣跟A字裙時髦多了
Can I get a blue bow?
可以給我個粉藍色的蝴蝶結嗎？
Okay. I have looked through a bunch of career guides..
好了，我看過很多的就業情報…
photocopied and highlighted key passages..
拷貝好並劃線標示出重要訊息…
and put them into alphabetical folders, so you can make an informed decision.
然後以字母分類歸檔 讓你可以做正確的決定
How long was I in there?
我在裡面多久了？
Okay, let's start with the A's. Advertising.
好了，我們先從A開始 廣告
Wait. Advertising, that's a great idea.
等一下，廣告，這是很棒的主意
Don't you wanna look through the rest?
你不想要聽別的了嗎？
I don't think I have to hear the rest. Advertising makes perfect sense.
我想我不用聽別的了 廣告最適合了
Sorry you had to waste all this time.
很抱歉浪費你這麼多時間
You call eight hours alone with my label maker wasted time?
你是說八小時 加上使用標籤機是浪費時間？
Now I'll get to use my shredder!
現在可以用上我的碎紙機了！
I mean, I could write slogans. How hard could it be, right?
我可以創作廣告口號的 能有多難呢？是不是？
"Cheese. It's milk that you chew."
「起司，是可以咬的牛奶」
"Crackers. Because your cheese needs a buddy."
「餅乾，是起司的良伴」
"A grape. Because who can get a watermelon in your mouth?"
「葡萄，因為整顆西瓜塞不進嘴裡」
I got one.
我想到一個
"Socks. Because your family's feet deserve the best."
「襪子，因為你家人的腳 值得用最好的」
Honey, leave it to the pros.
親愛的，讓專業的人說好嗎？
I actually know someone in advertising.
我認識一個在廣告業工作的人
I grew up with a guy who is a vice president at a big agency.
我跟他從小玩到大 現在他是一家大廣告公司的副總
Maybe I can get him to meet you. Give me the phone.
或許我可以請他跟你談談 把電話給我
"The phone. Bringing you closer to people who have phones."
「電話，讓你跟有電話的人更貼近」
"Marriage. It's not for everybody."
「婚姻，不是每個人都適合的」
That went well. Almost everybody knew that she was a girl.
真不錯，幾乎大家都知道她是女的
Yeah, after you punched that one guy who got it wrong, word spread.
是啊，在你揍了那個搞錯的男的之後 大家很快就知道了
I'm just gonna go in my office and pick up some stuff.
我要進去我辦公室拿點東西
- Who the hell are you? - Who the hell are you?
-你是誰？ -你是誰？
I'm the hell person whose office this is.
我是擁有這間辦公室的人
Good one, Rach.
說的好，瑞秋
I'm Gavin Mitchell, the person who's taking over your job.
我是蓋文米丘 那個要接替你工作的人
Excuse me?
什麼？
Your baby's so cute.
你的寶寶真可愛
But why would you put a pink bow on a boy?
但是為什麼在男生頭上 別個粉紅色蝴蝶結呢？
Hey, Joey. Look at me.
嘿，喬伊，看看我
I'm a nurse.
我是護士耶
Yes, you are.
是啊，你是
I think it might be time for my sponge bath.
我想該是擦海棉澡的時候了
Sorry, I'm just so used to hitting on the extras.
對不起，我太習慣泡臨時演員了
- So are you excited about your scene? - Yeah, but I'm a little nervous.
-你很期待出場嗎？ -是啊，但是我有點緊張
Relax. Don't be. They'll probably just make you stand in the background.
放輕鬆，別緊張 他們可能只會要你站在後面
- Good. - You. Here, come here. Here.
-很好 -你，這裡，過來，這裡
Take this tray, stand on this yellow mark. You're gonna move on "action."
拿著這個托盤，站在黃線這裡 聽到「開拍」就開始移動
Walk over to the operating table, stop on the blue mark and put the tray down.
走過去手術台，停在藍線那邊 然後把托盤放下
Don't walk too fast.
別走太快
But don't dawdle.
但是也別拖拉
Okay. Now, what?
好的，現在是怎樣呢？
And, action!
開拍！
Cut! Cut.
停！停！
- I'm sorry. I'm just a little nervous. - Well, don't be.
-我很抱歉，我只是有點緊張 -那就別緊張
Okay, that helps.
好的，真是幫了大忙
And, action!
開拍！
Cut!
停！
Don't worry about it, Phoebe. It usually takes me three takes too.
別擔心，菲比 我通常也是要三次才行
All right, eight.
好啦，八次
And, action!
開拍！
So do you have any other questions about advertising?
那你對於廣告還有其他的問題嗎？
No. But let me show you what I can do.
沒有，但是讓我表演一下我專長
"Bagels and doughnuts.
貝果跟甜甜圈…
Round food for every mood."
任何心情都適合吃的圓圈圈
Monica warned me you might do that.
摩妮卡警告過我，你可能會這樣做
I think we might have something for you at the agency.
我想我們公司可能有個適合你的職務
- Really? That's great. - It's an unpaid internship.
-真的嗎？太好了 -有個不支薪的實習職缺
That's funny. When you said "unpaid, " it sounded like you said "unpaid."
真好笑，當你說「不支薪」的時候 聽起來好像是「不支薪」的意思
It won't be forever. It just takes a year or two to get good portfolio together.
又不是永久的，只是要一至兩年 來建立好的工作經歷
Well, I can skip a couple of steps, right? I mean, you did hear my round food thing.
嗯，我可以省幾個步驟吧？不是嗎？ 你有聽到我具創意的圓形食物廣告詞啊
You're changing careers. No matter what you do, you'll have to start at the bottom.
你在轉業中，不管你怎樣努力 你都需要從基層做起的
It's gonna be years before you're making anything near as much as you were before.
要到達你之前的階級 你還有好幾年要努力
So you're paying the check, right?
所以你會買單，對嗎？
Come on, now. Monica has a good job. It's not like you have a family to support.
別這樣，摩妮卡有份很不錯的工作 又不是說你有家庭要養
Actually, we're trying. I don't think Monica is gonna want to postpone it.
事實上，我們正在努力做人 我不認為摩妮卡想要延期
We're supposed to have sex tonight.
我們今晚應該要做愛的
Actually, she's probably at home, naked right now.
事實上，現在她或許就已經 光著身體在家了
I tend to keep talking till somebody stops me.
如果沒有人阻止我，我會一直說話
- I can just picture her on the bed. - Stop!
-我可以想像她在床上的樣子 -停！
Wait. What do you mean you're taking over my job?
等等，你是什麼意思 要接替我的工作？
While you were on your baby vacation, I was doing your job.
當你去度你的育嬰假的時候 你的工作是我在做的
A vacation? My idea of a vacation does not involve..
假期？我對假期的定義可不包含…
something sucking on my nipples until they are raw.
讓什麼東西吸我的乳房 吸到破皮
Clearly, you've never been to Sandals Paradise lsland.
顯而易見地，你從未去過 天體營渡假小島
All right. Don't get too comfortable there, because I'm back in two weeks.
好了，別讓你自己太舒服 因為我兩個星期之後就回來了
I want everything back the way it was.
我要一切回歸原狀
I can't say I care too much for the way you've rearranged my office.
我實在不太滿意 你重新擺設我辦公室的方式
I can't say I care too much for that smell you've brought in.
我實在不太滿意那股你帶進來的味道
- Excuse me? - Rach, we have a code brown situation.
-你說什麼？ -瑞秋，我們有個棕色警戒狀況
Honey, could you please take care of it for me?
親愛的，可以拜託你幫我處理一下嗎？
All right, but you're gonna have to do one sometime.
好吧，但是有時候你也該處理一次
Let me just get this straight.
讓我把話說清楚
So I go have a baby, and they send some guy in to do my job?
我去生個小孩 然後他們派一個人過來接我的工作？
Well, there was talk of shutting down Ralph Lauren altogether.
嗯，本來有說要關閉整個洛夫羅倫的
Okay. Right. You're very cheeky for a temp.
好了，你只不過是個不要臉的臨時工
I'm not a temp. I was transferred here from another department.
我不是臨時工 我是從別的部門調過來的
And what department was that? The jerk department?
是什麼部門呢？渾蛋部門嗎？
They didn't tell me about your quick wit.
他們並沒有告訴我，你反應是如此快
Well, did they mention that I'm rubber and you're glue?
那他們也沒有告訴你 我是橡皮擦、你是膠水嗎？
- Gavin, Ralph loved your ideas. - Hi, Mr. Zelner.
-蓋文，洛夫很喜歡你的創意 -嗨，塞納先生
Rachel. I see you've met Gavin.
瑞秋，我想你見過蓋文了
When you left us, we weren't sure what we were gonna do.
當你離開的時候 我們都不知道該怎麼辦
But then, Gavin to the rescue. Super Gavin.
但是，蓋文拯救了我們 超級蓋文
Well, that's great.
喔，太好了
So now, Super Gavin, when I come back..
那麼，超級蓋文，當我回來以後…
where do you plan on flying off to?
你計劃要飛到哪去呢？
That's up to Mr. Zelner. I'm sure he'll make the right decision.
全看賽納先生的意思 我相信他會做出正確的決定
Super ass-kissing power.
超級馬屁精
Incidentally, when are you coming back?
對了，你什麼時候要回來呢？
Today.
今天
- You said two weeks. - No, I said today.
-你剛剛不是說兩星期後 -不，我是說今天
See, for a superhero, not so much with the listening.
看吧，身為超級英雄 聽話能力可也不怎麼樣
I'm sorry. Rachel, we should probably go.
我很抱歉，瑞秋，我們該走了
I ran out of diapers, and I had to use your sweater.
尿片用完了，我得用你的毛衣代替
- I didn't bring a sweater. - Then, we should really go.
-我沒有帶毛衣來 -那麼我們最好趕快走
So, what'd he say?
那他怎麼說呢？
He can be a little rough around the edges..
他有時候有點粗暴…
so I'm gonna replace a word he used a lot with the word "puppy."
所以我要「小狗」 代換掉他常用的一個字眼
So he said, "If your puppy friend doesn't get her puppy act together..
他說如果你的小狗朋友 不把小狗的角色演好…
I am gonna fire her mother-puppy ass."
我將會小狗的開除她
I'm sorry. I can't do this. I'm just not an actor.
我很抱歉，我辦不到 我不是演員的料
That's right. You're not. You're a nurse.
沒錯，你不是演員，你是護士
- You're Nurse With Tray. - No, Joey..
-你是拿托盤的護士 -不，喬伊…
Nurse With Tray doesn't know Joey. She has no time for friends.
拿托盤的護士不認識喬伊的 她沒有時間交朋友
She gets in that operating room and she carries that tray to the doctor..
她進去手術室把托盤交給醫生…
because if she doesn't, people die.
因為如果她不這樣做，有人會死的
Who dies?
誰會死？
Man With Eye Patch!
戴眼罩的男人！
Now, you get in there, and you do your job.
現在你過去做好你的工作
Yes, doctor.
是的，醫師
Okay, let's try this one more time.
好了，我們再試一次
Hang in there, Man With Eye Patch. Your tray is coming.
撐著點，戴眼罩的男人 你的托盤來了
And, action.
開拍
Yes, I did it! I nailed it!
是的，我辦到了！我搞定了！
What's next?
接下來是什麼呢？
The rest of the scene.
是後面的劇情
Okay, from the top, people.
好的，大家，從頭開始
Hey, you know what I was thinking? I don't know if "code brown" is the best code word.
嘿，你知道我在想什麼嗎？ 我不知道「棕色警戒」是不是好的暗號
I think people might know what we're talking about.
我想大家可能都猜得到我們在說什麼
That's fine. Listen, sudden change of plans. My maternity leave just ended.
沒關係，聽著，計劃改變 我的產假要結束了
They said if I didn't come back today, they'd fire me.
他們說如果我不今天回去工作 他們就要開除我
What? No, that's illegal.
什麼？那樣是非法的
I'll have the Labor Department here so fast, they won't..
我要馬上通知勞委會，他們不…
All right, calm down, Norma Rae. They didn't actually say that.
沒關係，冷靜點，柯賜海 他們並沒有真的那樣說
I'm just afraid if I don't come back now, this guy will try and squeeze me out.
我只是害怕如果不現在回去 那個男的會把我擠掉
But what about Emma? I mean, we don't have a nanny.
那艾□怎麼辦呢？我們還沒有找到保姆
I know. We're just gonna have to figure out a plan tonight.
我知道，我們只好今晚再想辦法了
Can you please just take care of her for today?
今天你可以先照顧她嗎？
Absolutely. Just give me your breasts, and we'll be on our way.
當然，只要給我你的胸部 我們馬上就走
Come on. I don't know what else to do.
別這樣，我不知道還能怎麼辦
Fine. Fine.
好啦，好啦
We'll have fun, won't we? Yes, we will. Yes, we..
我們會很開心的，不是嗎？ 是的，我們會，是的，我們…
Ross.
羅斯
You're pretty.
你好漂亮
Whatever I decide to do, I'm gonna be starting a new career from scratch.
不管我決定要做什麼 我都得從基層做起
It's gonna be a while before I make a living at it.
要一陣子我才有辦法真正賺些錢
Maybe now's not the right time to be starting a family.
或許現在不是生小孩的好時機
So you have to tell Monica you don't want to have a baby right now?
所以你要跟摩妮卡說 你現在不想要生小孩？
Yeah.
是啊
Goodbye.
再見了
Okay, it's baby time. Pants off, Bing.
好了，生小孩時間 褲子脫掉，賓
Didn't see you there, Geller.
沒看到你也在，蓋勒
Ross is here, so..
羅斯在這裡，所以…
And I was really hoping that maybe I could hang out.
我真的希望，可以跟你們待在一起
You know, what do you feel like doing?
你們想要做什麼呢？
Well, we're gonna have sex.
我們想要做愛
I don't feel like having sex.
我倒是不太想做愛
Maybe.. I don't know. Maybe we can watch a movie or something.
或許…我不知道 或許我們可以一起看電影什麼的
Let me put it this way:
讓我這樣說好了
We're having sex whether you're here or not.
不管你在不在，我們都要做愛
Pants off, Bing.
褲子脫掉，賓
Now that I'm back, why don't you just fill me in on what you've been up to.
現在既然我回來了 何不告訴我你做了什麼
Well, I've changed your screen saver from that picture of *NSYNC.
嗯，我把你NSYNC的螢幕保護程式改了
Hey, they were popular when I left.
嘿，我離開時那可是很受歡迎的
I'm working on this big presentation for tomorrow.
我在準備明天的一個重要報告
I should be involved in that, so get me up to speed.
我應該要參與，跟我說明吧
That'll take weeks. Let me take care of the presentation.
那可會花上好幾個星期 讓我處理這個報告就可以了
No. I see what you're doing here, all right?
不，我知道你在玩什麼花樣，好嗎？
This is my job, buddy. I've had it for five years, and I know how it works.
這是我的工作，我已經做了五年了 我知道一切流程
- So why don't you just catch me up. - Fine.
-所以趕快跟我解釋 -好
Oh, God. You've totally messed with the back support on my chair.
天啊，你把我椅子的高度完全變了
- How do you fix this? - You've been here five years.
-你是怎麼弄的？ -你已經在這裡五年了
- You figure it out. - Fine, I will.
-你自己想 -很好，我自己來
All right, fill me in.
好了，跟我說吧
Do you have a blue tie that would go with this? Emma spit up on mine.
你有沒有藍色的領帶跟這配？ 艾□吐奶到我的領帶上
Yeah, but you have to give it back if I get a job.
有啊，但是如果我找到工作時要還我
Of course, by that time, ties will be obsolete..
當然，到那時候 領帶已經被淘汰了…
and we'll all be wearing silver jumpsuits.
而我們將全都穿起銀色的連身裝
Hey, good morning, lover.
早安，愛人
I gotta say, after last night, I'm a little weak in the knees.
我得要說，在經過昨夜之後 我的雙腿還在發軟
Here's an idea. You walk into a room, take a quick scan.
麻煩你，每次走進來的時候 先快速看一下四周吧
Sorry.
抱歉
But I kind of have this feeling that we may have made a baby last night.
但是我有點覺得 我們昨晚做人成功了
Oh, God, I have to tell you something.
喔，天，我必須告訴你一件事
You're not pregnant.
你沒有懷孕
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
Well, that thing that I have to do to make a baby?
嗯，那件能使你懷孕的事？
I faked it.
我裝的
What? You faked it?
什麼？你裝的？
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I don't need a tie.
我不需要領帶了
I mean, it's better open collar, you know?
我是說領子開著比較好，不是嗎？
It's more casual.
比較輕鬆自在
Joey. Listen, I can't do this. It doesn't make any sense.
喬伊，聽著，我辦不到 這實在是沒有道理
Yesterday I was a nurse, and today I'm a waitress at a cafe?
昨天我是護士，然後今天我是服務生？
Sometimes we use the same extras for different parts. It's okay.
有時候我們會用相同的臨時演員 扮演不同的角色，沒關係的
Well, it's not okay, because I gave a very memorable performance as the nurse.
是有關係的 因為昨天我扮演護士，演的相當好
And now, suddenly, I'm the waitress? That's gonna confuse my fans.
然後現在突然間，我變成服務生？ 我的影迷會混淆的
Well, maybe you are a nurse..
嗯，或許你是護士…
but you moonlight as a waitress.
但是你也兼差當服務生
Because I'm a single mother supporting my two children.
因為我是扶養兩個小孩的單親媽媽
Nice.
沒錯
Wait a minute.
等一下
Dr. Drake Ramoray and I work at the same hospital. Wouldn't I come say hi?
德克羅孟瑞醫生跟我在同間醫院工作 我不用過來打招呼嗎？
No. No, see, you and Drake are having a fight.
不、不，你跟德克在吵架
About what?
吵什麼？
He slept with you.. Best sex you ever had, by the way.
他跟你上床… 順便一提，是你有過最美好的一次
And then never called you.
然後再也沒有打電話給你
And I just wanted a new daddy for Davey and Becky.
而我只想幫大衛跟貝琪找個新爸爸
Okay. Okay, from the top.
好了，好了，從頭開始
And, action.
開拍
So I'm surprised you agreed to have lunch with me.
我很訝異你會同意跟我用午餐
I'm surprised too. But yet, here I am.
我也很訝異，但我終究是來了
Cut! Cut!
卡！卡！
What are you doing?
你是在做什麼？
I'm very angry at him because he slept with me and never called me back.
我很氣他，因為他跟我上過床之後 就再也沒有打電話給我了
- Me too. - Me too!
-我也是 -還有我！
Calm down. She means on the show.
冷靜點，她是說在劇情裡面
We need some new extras around here.
我們需要新的臨時演員
Wow. You're here already.
哇，你已經到了
Yes. Emma and I came in a little early to do research on the presentation.
是的，艾□跟我提早進來準備報告
Actually, I made a few changes. I think I'm caught up on everything.
事實上，我做了一些修改 我想我都準備好了
So ask me anything.
隨便問我一個問題吧
- How do you fix the chair? - Except that!
-你要怎麼調整椅子呢？ -除了這個！
Hello, Mr. Zelner. We are all ready for our presentation this afternoon.
哈囉，塞納先生，今天下午的報告 我們都已經準備好了
- Good, because it's in 10 minutes. - What? I can't do that. I have the baby.
-很好，因為十分鐘之後就要開始了 -什麼？我沒辦法，我寶寶在這裡
Ross is not gonna pick her up for an hour.
羅斯一個小時之後才會來接她
Then Gavin can give the presentation. We have to do it now.
那蓋文可以上台報告 我們現在就要開始了
Ralph needs to leave early today. He's going helicopter shopping.
洛夫今天要提早走 他要搭直升機去血拼
But I love that man. I'd follow him into hell.
但是我愛那個男人 連地獄我都會跟他去的
Microphones.
擴音器開著
Well, there you go, you win. You win.
好了，順你的意了，你贏了 你贏了
You get to do the presentation. You'll knock them dead.
你可以上台報告，讓他們愛死你
No one will remember that I worked here, and then Ralph will buy his helicopter..
沒有人會記得我在這裡工作過 然後洛夫會搭上直升機…
and Super Gavin will just fly right alongside of him.
還有超級蓋文跟他一起飛
- You can do the presentation. - No, I can't. I have a baby.
-你可以上台去報告 -不，我不行，我寶寶在這裡
I'll watch her.
我會看著她
Why would you do that?
你為什麼要這樣？
Because you worked really hard, and it's your job. And you're a little crazy.
因為你工作很辛苦，而這是你的工作 還有你有點瘋狂
That's really nice.
你真的很好
I should tell you that crying women make me very uncomfortable.
我應該告訴你 哭泣的女人讓我覺得很不自在
Well, you're not gonna like what's coming.
嗯，那你可能不會喜歡接著要發生的事
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉，我很抱歉 我很抱歉，我很抱歉
God.
天哪
Thank you. Thank you.
謝謝你，謝謝你
I'm really fine. Don't worry. I'm great with children.
我沒事的，別擔心 我很會帶小孩的
Gavin Mitchell. Pleased to meet you.
我是蓋文米丘，很高興認識你
Please don't fire my friend. Just let me talk to her.
請不要開除我的朋友 讓我先跟她談談
- Okay, but this is her last chance. - Thank you.
-好吧，但是這是她最後一次機會 -謝謝
How about I do something for you?
我幫你一個忙如何？
Tomorrow, I'll bring you a hat, cover up the bald.
明天，我幫你帶一頂帽子 讓你遮住禿頭
Listen, Phoebe. I was just talking to the director..
聽著菲比，我剛跟導演談完…
and he was thinking maybe this time you don't hit Drake.
他說或許，這一次你不要打德克
You just wait on the tables.
你只要端盤子就可以了
I can't do that. I'm an actor. I have a process.
我不能那樣做，我是演員 我有我的程序的
You're a masseuse. You have a table with a hole in it.
你是按摩師 你有的是挖了個洞的桌子
Wait, I see what's happening here. You're threatened.
等等，我知道這是怎麼回事了 你感到威脅了
What?
什麼？
I'm so good in the scene that I'm stealing focus from you.
我的演技好到搶了你的鋒頭
Rise to the challenge, Tribbiani, because I just raised the bar.
接受挑戰吧，崔比亞尼 因為我只會提高你的水準
Come join me up here.
提升自己、向我看齊吧
- Okay, great. I will. - Okay, good.
-好的，很好，我會的 -好，很好
Yeah, you can fire her, but I would call security. She won't go easy.
你可以開除她，但是最好叫保安過來 請神容易送神難哦
You faked it? You couldn't have faked it.
你裝的？你不可能裝的
Yes, you can. You just make the faces and the noises.
是可以的，只要裝點表情跟聲音
Guys can fake it?
男生可以裝嗎？
Unbelievable. The one thing that's ours.
不可思議，明明只有女生才會裝的
Why would you fake it when we're trying to have a baby?
為什麼在我們想要生小孩的時候 你卻要裝這種事呢？
Well, that's actually why.
嗯，這正是我要裝的原因
Look, I'm starting a whole new career now.
聽著，我正在換工作
I'm not saying I don't want a baby.
我不是說我不想要孩子
I'm just saying maybe we could wait a little while.
只是或許我們可以等一陣子
Like a month?
一個月嗎？
- Or a year? - Really? You wanna wait a year?
-或是一年？ -真的嗎？你想要等一年？
It could be less than a year. I mean, you've heard my stuff.
不用到一年，我是說 你知道我的能力
"Pants. Like shorts but longer."
「褲子，跟襯衫一樣，只是長一點」
It'll probably be more than a year.
可能會不只一年吧
- I really wanna have a baby. - Well, yeah, me too.
-我真的很想要生小孩 -嗯，是啊，我也是
Look, I'll just get my old job back.
聽著，我回去做老本行好了
No, I want you to have a job that you love..
不，我要你做你熱愛的工作
not statistical analysis and data reconfiguration.
不是什麼數據分析跟資料重組的
I quit, and you learn what I do?
我辭職後，你才瞭解我在做什麼？
I think there's never gonna be a right time to have a baby.
我想永遠不會有適合生小孩的時機的
Now you're unemployed, and in a little while..
現在你失業了，但一陣子過後…
you'll find a new job that'll keep you really busy.
你就會找到一份讓你忙不過來的工作
There's always gonna be a reason not to do this..
總是會有理由不能生小孩的
but I think once the baby comes, we'll forget about all those reasons.
但是我想，一但有了孩子 我們就會忘了這一切的理由
I guess.
我想也是
I mean, it's always gonna be scary when we have a baby.
我是說，有小孩總是很嚇人的事
It's gonna be really scary.
真的會是很嚇人的
I mean, God, when we have a baby..
當我們有小孩的時候…
there's gonna be so much that we're not able to control.
將會有許多事情我們無法控制
I mean, the apartment's gonna be a mess.
我是說這間公寓將會一團亂
I won't have time to clean it.
我會沒有時間整理
What if the baby gets into the ribbon drawer..
要是寶寶跑到緞帶抽屜裡…
and messes up all the ribbons?
把所有的緞帶都弄亂了呢？
What if there's no room for a ribbon drawer..
萬一沒有地方可以放緞帶…
because the baby's stuff takes up all the space?
所有的空間都被寶寶東西佔滿了呢？
Where will all the ribbons go?
緞帶要放哪呢？
Should we go make a baby before you change your mind?
該不該在你改變主意之前 趕快去做人？
- Yes, please! - Okay.
-是啊，拜託快點！ -好的
And I promise I will not fake it this time.
而且我保證，這一次我不會裝了
Well, I wish I could say the same. I'm a little shook up.
嗯，我希望我也可以說相同的話 我現在有點激動
I know you botched that operation on purpose.
我知道你故意手術失敗的
I can't prove it yet, but when I do, you'll be going to jail for murder.
我還沒有辦法證明，但是當我可以時 你會因謀殺而坐牢的
I don't care if you are my brother.
我不在乎你是不是我弟弟
I'm not your brother.
我不是你弟弟
What about my children, Drake?
我的孩子怎麼辦呢？德克
No! No! No!
不！不！不！
God!
天啊！